Guide to the Yale Repertory Theatre Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Repertory Theatre records
1941-2003
RU 148
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
77.25
The records consist of personnel files, performance schedules, photographs and slides, posters, correspondence, memoranda, notes, reports, surveys, cast lists, reviews, budget materials, scripts, brochures, and accounting records documenting the management and activities of the Yale Repertory Theatre and its Winterfest productions.
Yale Repertory Theatre
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 22-E (YRG 22-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Drama.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of personnel files, performance schedules, photographs and slides, posters, correspondence, memoranda, notes, reports, surveys, cast lists, reviews, budget materials, scripts, brochures, and accounting records documenting the management and activities of the Yale Repertory Theatre and its Winterfest productions.
Repertory theater; Theater management; Theater; Photographs; Yale Repertory Theatre; Yale School of Drama; Yale University -- Administration
- Company management and Winterfest records, circa 1980-1990; Accession 1994-A-076
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  - Master Contact Sheet, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Office of Foreign Students and Scholars, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Employee Info Sheets, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Comp lCOD Request Forms, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Fanshen, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Employee Info Forms, completed, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - House of York, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Hello and Goodbye, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Hiring Forms [I], circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Hiring Forms [II], circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Hiring Forms [ID], circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - A Touch of the Poet (Rep VI), circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Lower Depths, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Map Dittos, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - A Touch of the Poet, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Parking Info, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Philanderer, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Production Calendar, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - School Shows (projects), circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Script Distribution, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Tax Notice, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - [Calendar, Script, Notes,], 1981- 1982 (Box 1)
  - Rip Hiring Forms, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - [Evaluations ], circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence (Miscellaneous), circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Apartment Rent Receipts, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Boesman Contact Sheets plus Addendum, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Boesman Notices, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Yale Cabaret Memo, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Boesman and Lena: Notices/Schedule, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Boesman and Lena: Contact Sheets, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Complementary Ticket Policy, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Equity Notices for Season, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - Suicide - Contact Sheet, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Suicide - Cast List, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Suicide - Notices, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Suicide - Extras, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Twelfth Night - Contact Sheets, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Hedda Gabler - Memos, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Hedda Gabler - Actor Contact Sheet, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Twelfth Night - Notices, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Twelfth Night - Performance Schedule, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Winterfest: Contact Sheets, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Winterfest: Domestic Issues, Contact Sheet, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Winterfest: Rococo Contact Sheet, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Winterfest: Schedule, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Sally and Marsha - Actor Contact Sheet, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Lady Lester - Actor Contact Sheet, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Hedda Gabler - Contact Sheet (Staff), circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Magnificent Cuckold - Staff Contact Sheet, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Magnificent Cuckold - Actor Contact, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Attempt at Flying - Staff Contact Sheet, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Bakkhai - Contact Sheets, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Bakkhai - Revised Performance Schedule, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Bakkhai - Notices, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Life is a Dream - Contact Sheets, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Life is a Dream - Notices, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Peer Gynt - Contact Sheets, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Summerfolk - Contact Sheets, circa 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Pygmalion - Housing, 1990 (Box 1)
  - [ Pygmalion, miscellaneous], 1990 (Box 1)
  - Pygmalion Pert: Reports, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Pygmalion - Hiring forms, 1990 (Box 1)
  - ACM Cash Advance, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Season Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Season Housing and Commutation, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Season Cast Lists, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Season Rehearsal Schedules, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Season Telephone Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Warrior Ant - Special Project, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Intermezzo Rep I Season: Press, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Intermezzo Rep I Season: Hiring Forms, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Intermezzo Rep I Season: Performance Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Intermezzo Rep I Season: Notes, Memos, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Intermezzo Rep I Season: Contact Sheets, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman Rep 2: Pre-production Notes, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman Rep 2: Hiring Forms, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman Rep 2: Rehearsal Notes, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman Rep 2: Contact Sheets, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman Rep 2: Notes, Memos, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - 1st Years General (Box 2)
  - Hotel Reservations, 1989-90 (Box 2)
  - Apt. Info 297 George St., circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - Rent America, circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - Company Management, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Dressing Room Assignments Season, 1989-90 (Box 2)
  - Handbook, circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - Expense Reports, 1989-90 (Box 2)
  - Winterfest 9 Season: Notes, Memos, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Foreign Students and Scholars Info, circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - Housing Information, circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - Apartment Furnishings, circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - To Do, circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - First Rehearsal [Winterfest], 1989-90 (Box 2)
  - [Contracts], circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - [Miscellaneous], circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - Seminars, circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - Winterfest 6 Season, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Winterfest Seminars, circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Completed Audience Surveys, circa 1985-1990 (Box 2)
  - Season, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Contact Sheets, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Ivanov, circa 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Largo Desolato, circa 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - [Calendar: Search and Destroy ], circa 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Two Trains Running, circa 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Search and Destroy, circa 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Winterfest/Trillin, circa 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Underground, circa 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Production Notes from S.M. and Tech [SGC], circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Performance Reports [ Solid Gold Cadillac ], circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Actor Info: Hiring Forms and Em.MOO., circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Solid Gold Cadillac, circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Coman. SGC [ Solid Gold Cadillac ], circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Production Notes [ Miss Julie ], circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Actor Info: Hiring Forms and Em.MOO., circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Miss Julie, circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Summer and Smoke, circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Performance Reports [ Summer and Smoke ], circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Production Notes [ Summer and Smoke ], circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Actor Info: Hiring Forms and Medical, circa 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Housing WF [Winterfest Xl, 1990 (Box 3)
  - WF-10 Performance Reports, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Winterfest General [X], 1990 (Box 3)
  - Hiring Forms D.E. [ Daylight in Exile ], 1990 (Box 3)
  - [ Dinosaurs: miscellaneous], 1990 (Box 3)
  - Hiring Forms [ Dinosaurs ], 1990 (Box 3)
  - Hiring Forms P.R. [ Pill Hill ], 1990 (Box 3)
  - [ Rust and Ruin: miscellanea], 1990 (Box 3)
  - Hiring Forms: R and R [ Rust and Rui n], 1990 (Box 3)
  - Medical Forms [ Troilus and Cressida ], 1990 (Box 3)
  - Troilus - Performance Reports, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Hiring Forms TandC [ Troilus and Cressida ], 1990 (Box 3)
  - TandC Production Notes [ Troilus and Cressida ], 1990 (Box 3)
  - Two Trains - Notes, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Emergency Medical Forms [ Two Trains Running ], 1990 (Box 3)
  - Two Trains - Performance Reports, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Two Trains - Hiring Forms, 1990 (Box 3)
  - [ Two Trains Running: miscellaneous], 1990 (Box 3)
  - [Staff Meeting Notes and Miscellaneous], 1980 (Box 3)
  - Benten Kozo: Staff and Cast Sheets, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Tartuffe and Learned Ladies: Staff Contact Sheet, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Rep II: P.M.'s Files, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Production Memos- Out (Extra), circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - (Management: miscellaneous], circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Permanent File (out of everything), circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Co. Mgr. [Hiring Forms,etc], circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Misc. Cast Lists/Student Projects, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Cast Lists (School Shows), circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Baal - STI - Contact Sheet, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Baal - Notices, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - STW Long Days Journey: Contact Sheet, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - STW Long Days Journey: Notices, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - Spring Awakening - Student III, 1981 (Box 3)
  - As I Lay Dying, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Pillars Contact, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - As I Lay Dying - Company Memo, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Winter's Tale, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Hiring Contracts: Uncle Vanya, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - Uncle Vanya Rep I: Notices and Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - Vanya Contact Sheets: Staff and Cast, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - Hiring Forms: Mrs. Warren's Profession, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession Rep II: Notices/Corr., circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Rip Van Winkle: Contact Sheets and Notices, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Rip Van Winkle Rep 3 Notices, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Rip Van Winkle Rep 3 Correspondence and Memos, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Winterfest Contact [II], 1982 (Box 3)
  - Winterfest Memos [II], 1982 (Box 3)
  - Hiring for Winterfest [II], 1982 (Box 3)
  - Winterfest Information [II], 1982 (Box 3)
  - Master Harold...and the Boys, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Master Harold and the Boys - Actor and Contact Sheets, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Johnny Bull - Hiring Forms, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Johnny Bull - Misc., circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - LLL [ Love's Labours Lost ] - Misc., circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Neapolitan Ghosts - Press/Reviews, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Heartbreak House - Press/Reviews, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Neapolitan Ghosts - Memos/Postings, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - The Winter's Tale - Press/Reviews, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Winterfest - Press/Reviews, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Walk in the Woods, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - A Place With the Pigs, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Elizabeth, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Winterfest - Playwrights/Directors/Stage Managers [7], 1987 (Box 3)
  - The Winter's Tale - Memos/Postings, circa 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - Dona Wright's Contract Work File, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Moving to 5 Rep Shows, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - [expenses], circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - ASTI, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - ASTI: Meeting Notes, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - ASTI: Receipts, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Glasnost Project, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Glasnost Cabaret - Receipts, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - [ASTI miscellaneous], circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - [General Administration, classes of 1991 and 1992], circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Residency and Receipts, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Residency, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Contact Sheet, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Daily ("To Do's"), circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Billing, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Chorus Members, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Press circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Contract/Rhys Williams, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Running Crew Contracts, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Co-Production Agreements, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Cash Flow, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Budgets (Old), circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Budget [new], circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Insurance Letters, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Letters - Foundation Support, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Copies of Receipts- Pre-Production, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Security, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Inventory, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Rentals, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Sound/Electrics, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Housing, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Rehearsal/Performance Reports, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Rehearsal/Performance Schedule, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Tech, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Notes from Production Meeting, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Thank you Notes, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Casuals, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Warrior Ant: Calendar, miscellaneous, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Transposed Heads [Budget], circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Special Project - Eric Bogosian, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Kennedy Center: Memos and Correspondence, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Kennedy Center: Tickets, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Kennedy Center: Roommates/Hotel, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Emergency Medical Forms, circa 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - History [ Winterfest ], circa 1983-1987 (Box 4)
  - Budget [ Winterfest V ], 1985 (Box 4)
  - Columbia Pies, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Wooster Group, circa 1983-1987 (Box 4)
  - Actor's Equity, circa 1983-1987 (Box 4)
  - Calendar, circa 1983-1987 (Box 4)
  - Calls [ Winterfest V ], 1985 (Box 4)
  - Calls [ Winterfest VI ], 1986 (Box 4)
  - Clippings, circa 1983-1987 (Box 4)
  - Contracts, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Dracula, circa 1983-1987 (Box 4)
  - East Meets West [Between East and West], 1985 (Box 4)
  - Faulkner's Bicycle, circa 1983-1987 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence [ Winterfest V ], 1985 (Box 4)
  - Casting, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Memos In [ Winterfest V ], 1985 (Box 4)
  - Memos Out [ Winterfest V ], 1985 (Box 4)
  - Memos Out [ Winterfest VI ], 1986 (Box 4)
  - Notes for/from Meetings, circa 1983-1987 (Box 4)
  - Press, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Producer Letter, circa 1983-1987 (Box 4)
  - Rum and Coke, circa 1983-1987 (Box 4)
  - Memos In, 1985/86 (Box 4)
  - Expenses [ Winterfest VI ], 1986 (Box 4)
  - Seminar Speakers (Bios), 1986 (Box 4)
  - Seminars [ Winterfest V ], 1985 (Box 4)
  - Seminars [ Winterfest VI ], 1986 (Box 4)
  - Welcome Letter [ Winterfest VI ], 1986 (Box 4)
  - Winterfest Seminars 1984 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Letter Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Budget - WF Coor. Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Playreadings - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Banner - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Bio Info - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Calendar - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Calls - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Company Manage r- Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Development - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Sweatshirts/T-shirts - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Letters and Memos (sent) - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Ideas for Future Winterfests - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Seminar Ideas and Research and Programs - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Contact Sheets - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Group Sales - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Letters and Memos (received) - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Notes and Minutes - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Producer Letter - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Script Requests - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Seminar Correspondence - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Space - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Special Events - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Ticket Requests - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Press and Marketing, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Seminar Notes, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Casting - Understudies, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Columbia Pictures, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence with Lloyd, 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - General Letters and Memos Received, 1988 (Box 5)
  - General Overview Notes, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Performance Reports, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Artistic Directors/Producers Mailing, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Post-Play Discussions, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Bradley Fellowships [1987] (Box 5)
  - Playwrights Correspondence [1987-1988] (Box 5)
  - Budget [88/89] (Box 5)
  - Winterfest 8 Report, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Mailing, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Directors Correspondence, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Producers/Theaters Correspondence, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Production and Rehearsal Notes and Memos, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Prompters/Newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Seminar Posters and Stuffers, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Seminar Programs, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Winterfest Bulletin Board, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - General Memos and Letters Sent, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Budget, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Reception and Parties - Winterfest 7, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Seminar Correspondence, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Ticket Requests, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Contact Sheets, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Tote Bag Artwork, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Equity Info, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Financial Statements and Projections, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Playwrights Agreements - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Carol's Notes - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - First Rehearsal - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Banner - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Parties - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Development (Bradleys) - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Budget - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Rehearsal Space - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Contact Sheets - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Tote Bags - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Press - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Producer/Artistic Director List - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Misc. Memos - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Letter - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Productions Budget - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Director's Correspondence - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Meetings With Lloyd - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Playwright Correspondence - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Seminar Bios - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Ticket Requests - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Brochure - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Script Requests - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Casting - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - WeeklyPerformance Reports - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Rez Sisters (play Reading), circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Post-Play Discussions - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - PerformanceReports - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Rehearsal Schedules - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Tree Lights - Winterfest 9, 1989 (Box 5)
  - LORT/AEA Negotiations, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Susan Smith Blackburn Prize, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Rehearsal Notices [ Winterfest 10 ], 1990 (Box 5)
  - Voice Mail, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Banner, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Book Sales, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Box Office Summary, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Bradley Fellows [ Winterfest 11 ], 1991 (Box 5)
  - Budgets, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Cash Advance, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Contact Sheets [ Winterfest 11 ], 1991 (Box 5)
  - First Rehearsa1 [ Winterfest 11 ], 1991 (Box 5)
  - Winterfest Gifts, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Adrienne Kennedy Invites, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Lloyd Invites and Com. Producers and Artistic Dir., circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Misc. Winterfest [11], 1991 (Box 5)
  - WF (#10)- Notes for Reference, 1990 (Box 5)
  - WF Party, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Performance Reports, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Petty Cash Receipts, circa 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Playwright Travel, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Postage, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Press [ Winterfest 11 ], 1991 (Box 6)
  - Printing Fees, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Rehearsal Notes, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Rehearsal Schedules, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Rehearsal Spaces, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - WF Rush Tickets, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Tree Lights, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Work Study Hours, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Seminar Weekends- General Info, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Holiday Inn- Seminar Weekends, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Posters/Programs/Stuffers [ Winterfest 11 ], 1991 (Box 6)
  - Refreshments - Seminars, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Luis Francis - Seminar 2, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Susan Harjo - Seminar 2, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Abel Lopez - Seminar 3, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Sal Macri - Seminar 2, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Rob Marx, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Ruth Mayleas - Seminar 3, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Joe Melillo - Seminar 3, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Peter Sellars, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Don Shewer - Seminar 3, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Barbara Ann Teer, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - August Wilson - Seminar 1, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Stan Wojewodski, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Winterfest Ideas, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - WF Memos, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Pepsico, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Ivanov Taping, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Calvin Trillin, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Winterfest X /First Night New Haven, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Winterfest X Banner, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Winterfest X: Notes, Ideas, Working File, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Aids Benefit - Rep 6 Working File, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Winterfest X - Playreadings, 1990 (Box 6)
  - ASTI General Notes, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - ASTI Visits and Itineraries, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - ASTI Conference:Planning Notes, 1989 November 6-11 (Box 6)
  - ASTILogo, circa 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - House Seat Book/Producerand Artistic Directors, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Memos, Correspondence- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Playwrights: Housing, Traveland per diem-WF X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Seminar Notes, Correspondence, Honoraria-WFX, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Producer/Artistic Director Letter- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Contact Sheets, Phone Lists- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Bradley Fellowships- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Brochure Copy- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Casting- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence- Mailings and Scripts- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Winterfest Gift- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Performance Reports- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Press Articles- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Press Releases- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Production and Budget Meetings- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Rehearsal Schedules- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Schedules- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Stage Manager Weekly Rehearsal Reports-WFX, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Trade Ads- Winterfest X, 1990 (Box 6)
- Records of the Yale Repertory Theatre, circa 1941-2001; Accession 2003-A-022
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - 1999 -2000 Season
    - The Imaginary Invalid, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Betrayal, 10/21 -11/13/1999 (Box 1)
    - A Cup of Coffee, 11/26 -12/18/1999 (Box 1)
    - The Curse of the Starving Class, 2/3 -2/26/2000 (Box 1)